[Music]
[âm nhạc]
The sky is bright and clear, plump birds sing across
Trời tư tươi sáng chim béo von ngang
the sky, flowers and leaves are colorful,
trời hoa lá que sắc màu chư thiên chối
celestial music brings good news on the day of the Buddha,
nhạc trời tin mừng ngày đức Phật đan
Buddhists weep across the five continents, Buddhists weep across the
Phật tử khóc năm châu, Phật tử khóc địa
earth, rejoicing in the commemoration of the day of the Buddha's birth,
cầu tương vui kỳ niệm ngày Đức Phật đảng
asking the Buddha for compassion to create a flower chariot.  The Buddha sings, the
xin Phật từ kết xe hoa. Phật từ hát bồ
Bodhisattva respectfully celebrates the day of the Buddha's ceremony, the Buddha
tát kính mừng ngày đức Phật đàn
weeps, and together they form a flower chariot
xin Phật từ khóc nam châu cùng nhau kết
.  The Buddha wept as people from all five continents joined together in a procession of
xe hoa. Phật từ khóc năm châu cùng nhau
flower-decorated chariots.  Let us sing together to
dất xe hoa. Cùng nhau vui hát m ta kính
celebrate the day of the Buddha's birth
mừng ngày đức Phật đàn
[music]
[âm nhạc]
sky is bright and clear, birds sing, flowers and
Trời tươi tươi sáng chim béo von lan
leaves are colorful, the gods reject the
trời hoa lá que sắc màu chư thiên chối
heavenly house, good news of the day of the Buddha's birth
nhà trời tin mừng ngày đức Phật đàn
x Buddhists cry in the east, Buddhists cry on the earth,
x Phật tử khóc đông châ Phật tử khóc địa
joyful commemoration of the Buddha's birth, please Buddha, make a
câu từng vừng vui kỳ niệm ngài Đức Phật
flower float, Buddha sings, good
xin Phật từ kết xe hoa Phật từ hát ca
news of the day of the Buddha's birth, please Buddha cry, let us
tin mừng ngày Đức Phật đà
together make a
xin Phật từ khóc nam châu cùng nhau ghét
flower float, Buddha cry in the five continents, let us together
xe hoa Phật từ khóc năm châu cùng nhau
make a flower float, let us sing together to celebrate, bowing
dứt xe hoa cùng nhau vui hát ca kíh mừng
to the Buddha, please
lạy đức Phật đàn
Buddha, make a flower float, Buddha's seeds, celebrating
xin Phật từ kết xe hoa Phật từ hạt mố
the day of the Buddha's birth
Kính mừng ngày đức Phật đàn
x Buddhists from all five continents together make a
x Phật tử khắp năm châu cùng nhau kết xe
flower float.  From all five continents, together under the
hoa. Từ khắp năm châu cùng nhau dướt xe
flower-decorated chariot, together joyfully singing and celebrating the day of the
hoa cùng nhau vui hát mố kính mừng ngày
Buddha's
đức Phật đàn
assembly. We ask the Buddha to arrange the flower-decorated chariot, the Buddha to sing and
xin Phật từ kết xe hoa Phật từ hát mố ca
celebrate the day of the Buddha's assembly. We
kính mừng ngày đức Phật đan
ask the Buddhists from five continents to weep together under the
xin Phật tử khóc năm châu cùng nhau biết
flower-decorated chariot, the Buddhists from five continents to weep together
xe hoa Phật tử khóc năm châu cùng nhau
under the flower-decorated chariot, together joyfully singing and
dấtt xe hoa cùng nhau vui hát
celebrating the day of the assembly. We respectfully bow and pray
mừng ngày được phân tàn xin
to the Buddha.   A
Kính mừng lạy đức Phật đàn xin.
prayer celebrating the day the
Kinh mừng ngày Đức
Buddha is asking for
Phật đang xin
[music]
[âm nhạc]